{
  "categories": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "name": "Medical Coding",
      "subCategories": [
        {
          "id": "1-1",
          "name": "100 Word Parts",
          "flashCards": [
			  { "id": "1", "question": "gastr-", "answer": "Stomach" },
			  { "id": "2", "question": "cardi-", "answer": "Heart" },
			  { "id": "3", "question": "megal-", "answer": "Enlarged" },
			  { "id": "4", "question": "-itis", "answer": "Inflammation" },
			  { "id": "5", "question": "dermat-", "answer": "Skin" },
			  { "id": "6", "question": "plast-", "answer": "Surgical repair" },
			  { "id": "7", "question": "cerebr-", "answer": "Brain" },
			  { "id": "8", "question": "path-", "answer": "Disease" },
			  { "id": "9", "question": "-ectomy", "answer": "Surgical removal" },
			  { "id": "10", "question": "enter-", "answer": "Intestines" },
			  { "id": "11", "question": "-osis", "answer": "Any condition" },
			  { "id": "12", "question": "-otomy", "answer": "Cut into" },
			  { "id": "13", "question": "aden-", "answer": "gland" },
			  { "id": "14", "question": "angi-", "answer": "Vessel" },
			  { "id": "15", "question": "-oma", "answer": "Tumor" },
			  { "id": "16", "question": "nephr-", "answer": "Kidney" },
			  { "id": "17", "question": "hepat-", "answer": "Liver" },
			  { "id": "18", "question": "arthr-", "answer": "Joint" },
			  { "id": "19", "question": "blephar-", "answer": "eyelid" },
			  { "id": "20", "question": "-ologist", "answer": "Specialist" },
			  { "id": "21", "question": "rhin-", "answer": "Nose" },
			  { "id": "22", "question": "gingiv-", "answer": "gum" },
			  { "id": "23", "question": "-malacia", "answer": "Soft" },
			  { "id": "24", "question": "-ology", "answer": "The study of" },
			  { "id": "25", "question": "Spasm", "answer": "Involuntary contractions" },
			  { "id": "26", "question": "-algia", "answer": "pain" },
			  { "id": "27", "question": "crani-", "answer": "skull" },
			  { "id": "28", "question": "end-", "answer": "Inside, within" },
			  { "id": "29", "question": "hemi-", "answer": "half" },
			  { "id": "30", "question": "-oid", "answer": "like" },
			  { "id": "31", "question": "hyper-", "answer": "Above, more than normal" },
			  { "id": "32", "question": "cyst-", "answer": "Sac containing fluid" },
			  { "id": "33", "question": "chole-", "answer": "bile" },
			  { "id": "34", "question": "hypo-", "answer": "under" },
			  { "id": "35", "question": "-scop-", "answer": "observe" },
			  { "id": "36", "question": "hyster-", "answer": "uterus" },
			  { "id": "37", "question": "-ostomy", "answer": "Create an opening" },
			  { "id": "38", "question": "para-", "answer": "Beside, beyond" },
			  { "id": "39", "question": "-lysis", "answer": "Loosening, destruction" },
			  { "id": "40", "question": "cervic-", "answer": "neck" },
			  { "id": "41", "question": "chondr-", "answer": "cartilage" },
			  { "id": "42", "question": "cyan-", "answer": "blue" },
			  { "id": "43", "question": "hem(at)-", "answer": "blood" },
			  { "id": "44", "question": "ost-", "answer": "bone" },
			  { "id": "45", "question": "psycho-", "answer": "mind" },
			  { "id": "46", "question": "lip-", "answer": "fat" },
			  { "id": "47", "question": "my-", "answer": "muscle" },
			  { "id": "48", "question": "lith-", "answer": "stone" },
			  { "id": "49", "question": "opthalm- opt-", "answer": "Eye" },
			  { "id": "50", "question": "proct-", "answer": "Anus" },
			  { "id": "51", "question": "cost-", "answer": "Rib" },
			  { "id": "52", "question": "-gram", "answer": "Record" },
			  { "id": "53", "question": "acro-", "answer": "Extremities" },
			  { "id": "54", "question": "rhexis", "answer": "Break, burst" },
			  { "id": "55", "question": "carcin-", "answer": "Cancer" },
			  { "id": "56", "question": "-penia", "answer": "Decrease" },
			  { "id": "57", "question": "gen-", "answer": "Original, production" },
			  { "id": "58", "question": "burso-", "answer": "Sac" },
			  { "id": "59", "question": "retr(o)-", "answer": "Backwards" },
			  { "id": "60", "question": "trip-", "answer": "Rub, friction" },
			  { "id": "61", "question": "strept-", "answer": "Twist" },
			  { "id": "62", "question": "-desis", "answer": "Binding" },
			  { "id": "63", "question": "mani-", "answer": "Madness" },
			  { "id": "64", "question": "glosso-", "answer": "Tongue" },
			  { "id": "65", "question": "-trophy", "answer": "Development" },
			  { "id": "66", "question": "supra-", "answer": "Above" },
			  { "id": "67", "question": "-ptosis", "answer": "Falling" },
			  { "id": "68", "question": "-dyn-", "answer": "Pain" },
			  { "id": "69", "question": "mast-", "answer": "Breast" },
			  { "id": "70", "question": "-rrhaphy", "answer": "Suture" },
			  { "id": "71", "question": "dent-", "answer": "Teeth" },
			  { "id": "72", "question": "cephal-", "answer": "Head" },
			  { "id": "73", "question": "auto-", "answer": "Self" },
			  { "id": "74", "question": "epi-", "answer": "Upon" },
			  { "id": "75", "question": "hydro-", "answer": "Water" },
			  { "id": "76", "question": "lobo-", "answer": "Section" },
			  { "id": "77", "question": "-emesis", "answer": "Vomiting" },
			  { "id": "78", "question": "contra-", "answer": "Against, counter" },
			  { "id": "79", "question": "-iasis", "answer": "Condition" },
			  { "id": "80", "question": "trans-", "answer": "Through, across" },
			  { "id": "81", "question": "brady-", "answer": "Slow" },
			  { "id": "82", "question": "-ectasis", "answer": "Expansion" },
			  { "id": "83", "question": "cyt-", "answer": "Cell" },
			  { "id": "84", "question": "odont-", "answer": "Tooth" },
			  { "id": "85", "question": "leuk-", "answer": "White" },
			  { "id": "86", "question": "-esthesia", "answer": "Sensation" },
			  { "id": "87", "question": "cantho-", "answer": "Angle at the end of the eyelid" },
			  { "id": "88", "question": "steno-", "answer": "Narrow, contracted" },
			  { "id": "89", "question": "cheil-", "answer": "Lip" },
			  { "id": "90", "question": "-cele", "answer": "hernia" },
			  { "id": "91", "question": "benign", "answer": "Mild, not cancerous" },
			  { "id": "92", "question": "semen", "answer": "Seed" },
			  { "id": "93", "question": "celio-", "answer": "Abdomen" },
			  { "id": "94", "question": "erythro-", "answer": "Red" },
			  { "id": "95", "question": "vaso-", "answer": "Vessel" },
			  { "id": "96", "question": "melan-", "answer": "Black" },
			  { "id": "97", "question": "cauda-", "answer": "Tail" },
			  { "id": "98", "question": "lingua-", "answer": "Tongue" },
			  { "id": "99", "question": "myring-", "answer": "Eardrum" },
			  { "id": "100", "question": "spondyl-", "answer": "Spinal column" }
			]
        },
        {
          "id": "1-2",
          "name": "50 Abbreviations",
          "flashCards": [
			  { "id": "1", "question": "WBC", "answer": "White Blood Cells" },
			  { "id": "2", "question": "ENT", "answer": "Ears Nose & Throat" },
			  { "id": "3", "question": "AMA", "answer": "American Medical Association" },
			  { "id": "4", "question": "BP", "answer": "Blood Pressure" },
			  { "id": "5", "question": "dx", "answer": "Diagnosis" },
			  { "id": "6", "question": "RBC", "answer": "Red Blood Cell" },
			  { "id": "7", "question": "SOB", "answer": "Shortness of Breath" },
			  { "id": "8", "question": "WHO", "answer": "World Health Organization" },
			  { "id": "9", "question": "WNL", "answer": "Within Normal Limits" },
			  { "id": "10", "question": "OD", "answer": "Overdose" },
			  { "id": "11", "question": "CBC", "answer": "Complete Blood Count" },
			  { "id": "12", "question": "sx", "answer": "Symptoms" },
			  { "id": "13", "question": "bx", "answer": "Biopsy" },
			  { "id": "14", "question": "DM", "answer": "Diabetes Mellitus" },
			  { "id": "15", "question": "AKI", "answer": "Acute Kidney Injury" },
			  { "id": "16", "question": "CAD", "answer": "Coronary Artery Disease" },
			  { "id": "17", "question": "ASD", "answer": "Atrial Septal Defect" },
			  { "id": "18", "question": "COPD", "answer": "Chronic Obstructive Pulmonary Disease" },
			  { "id": "19", "question": "CVA", "answer": "Cerebrovascular Accident" },
			  { "id": "20", "question": "MI", "answer": "Myocardial Infarction" },
			  { "id": "21", "question": "OSA", "answer": "Obstructive Sleep Apnea" },
			  { "id": "22", "question": "TSH", "answer": "Thyroid Stimulating Hormone" },
			  { "id": "23", "question": "H&P", "answer": "History & Physical" },
			  { "id": "24", "question": "ROS", "answer": "Review of Symptoms" },
			  { "id": "25", "question": "ED", "answer": "Emergency Department" },
			  { "id": "26", "question": "ICU", "answer": "Intensive Care Unit" },
			  { "id": "27", "question": "CPT", "answer": "Current Procedural Terminology" },
			  { "id": "28", "question": "ICD", "answer": "International Classification of Disease" },
			  { "id": "29", "question": "OTC", "answer": "Over the Counter" },
			  { "id": "30", "question": "DJD", "answer": "Degenerative Joint Disease" },
			  { "id": "31", "question": "NSAID", "answer": "Non-Steroidal Anti-Inflammatory Drugs" },
			  { "id": "32", "question": "CHF", "answer": "Congestive Heart Failure" },
			  { "id": "33", "question": "TB", "answer": "Tuberculosis" },
			  { "id": "34", "question": "IUD", "answer": "Intrauterine Device" },
			  { "id": "35", "question": "LMP", "answer": "Last Menstrual Period" },
			  { "id": "36", "question": "TBSA", "answer": "Total Body Surface Area" },
			  { "id": "37", "question": "DVT", "answer": "Deep Vein Thrombosis" },
			  { "id": "38", "question": "PE", "answer": "Pulmonary Embolism" },
			  { "id": "39", "question": "TIA", "answer": "Transient Ischemic Attack" },
			  { "id": "40", "question": "CABG", "answer": "Coronary Artery Bypass Graft" },
			  { "id": "41", "question": "DDD", "answer": "Degenerative Disc Disease" },
			  { "id": "42", "question": "fx", "answer": "Fracture" },
			  { "id": "43", "question": "HTN", "answer": "Hypertension" },
			  { "id": "44", "question": "I&D", "answer": "Incision and Drainage" },
			  { "id": "45", "question": "IBS", "answer": "Irritable Bowel Syndrome" },
			  { "id": "46", "question": "IM", "answer": "Intramuscular" },
			  { "id": "47", "question": "PUD", "answer": "Peptic Ulcer Disease" },
			  { "id": "48", "question": "RA", "answer": "Rheumatoid Arthritis" },
			  { "id": "49", "question": "SQ", "answer": "Subcutaneous" },
			  { "id": "50", "question": "UTI", "answer": "Urinary Tract Infection" }
			]
        },
		{
          "id": "1-3",
          "name": "Terminology Prefixes",
          "flashCards": [
			{ "id": "1", "question": "a-", "answer": "Without", "example": "Atypical" },
			  { "id": "2", "question": "ab-", "answer": "Away from", "example": "Abduction" },
			  { "id": "3", "question": "ad-", "answer": "Increase", "example": "Adduction" },
			  { "id": "4", "question": "ante-", "answer": "Before", "example": "Antepartum" },
			  { "id": "5", "question": "anti-", "answer": "Against", "example": "Antipsychotic" },
			  { "id": "6", "question": "an-", "answer": "Without", "example": "Anoxia" },
			  { "id": "7", "question": "apo-", "answer": "Off, away from", "example": "Apophysis" },
			  { "id": "8", "question": "auto-", "answer": "Self", "example": "Autograph" },
			  { "id": "9", "question": "bi-", "answer": "Two, Twice", "example": "Bilateral" },
			  { "id": "10", "question": "bin-", "answer": "Double", "example": "Binocular" },
			  { "id": "11", "question": "brady-", "answer": "Slow", "example": "Bradycardia" },
			  { "id": "12", "question": "cata-", "answer": "Downwards", "example": "Catabolism" },
			  { "id": "13", "question": "con-", "answer": "With", "example": "Congenital" },
			  { "id": "14", "question": "diplo-", "answer": "Double", "example": "Diplopia" },
			  { "id": "15", "question": "de-", "answer": "Down, Without", "example": "Dehydrate" },
			  { "id": "16", "question": "dia-", "answer": "Completely", "example": "Dialysis" },
			  { "id": "17", "question": "dys-", "answer": "Abnormal", "example": "Dysphagia" },
			  { "id": "18", "question": "ec-", "answer": "Outside", "example": "Ectoderm" },
			  { "id": "19", "question": "endo-", "answer": "Within, in", "example": "Endotracheal" },
			  { "id": "20", "question": "epi-", "answer": "On, Upon", "example": "Epidermis" },
			  { "id": "21", "question": "eu-", "answer": "Normal, Good", "example": "Eupnea" },
			  { "id": "22", "question": "ex-", "answer": "Outwards", "example": "Exostosis" },
			  { "id": "23", "question": "extra-", "answer": "Outside of", "example": "Extrapleural" },
			  { "id": "24", "question": "hemi-", "answer": "Half", "example": "Hemicolectomy" },
			  { "id": "25", "question": "hetero-", "answer": "Different", "example": "Heterograft" },
			  { "id": "26", "question": "homo-", "answer": "Same", "example": "Homoplasty" },
			  { "id": "27", "question": "hyper-", "answer": "Excessive", "example": "Hyperthyroidism" },
			  { "id": "28", "question": "hypo-", "answer": "Incomplete", "example": "Hypoglycemia" },
			  { "id": "29", "question": "in-", "answer": "Inward", "example": "Inhalation" },
			  { "id": "30", "question": "infra-", "answer": "Beneath", "example": "Infra-axillary" },
			  { "id": "31", "question": "inter-", "answer": "Between", "example": "Intercostals" },
			  { "id": "32", "question": "intra-", "answer": "Within, in", "example": "Intramuscular" },
			  { "id": "33", "question": "juxta-", "answer": "Near", "example": "Juxta-articular" },
			  { "id": "34", "question": "macro-", "answer": "Large, Long", "example": "Macrocephalus" },
			  { "id": "35", "question": "mal-", "answer": "Abnormal", "example": "Malformation" },
			  { "id": "36", "question": "mega-", "answer": "Great", "example": "Megacolon" },
			  { "id": "37", "question": "meta-", "answer": "Change", "example": "Metastasis" },
			  { "id": "38", "question": "micro-", "answer": "Small", "example": "Microscope" },
			  { "id": "39", "question": "mono-", "answer": "One", "example": "Monochromatic" },
			  { "id": "40", "question": "morpho-", "answer": "Shape", "example": "Morphology" },
			  { "id": "41", "question": "multi-", "answer": "Many", "example": "Multipara" },
			  { "id": "42", "question": "neo-", "answer": "New", "example": "Neonate" },
			  { "id": "43", "question": "nulli-", "answer": "None", "example": "Nulligravida" },
			  { "id": "44", "question": "pachy-", "answer": "Thick", "example": "Pachyderma" },
			  { "id": "45", "question": "pan-", "answer": "All, Total", "example": "Pancytopenia" },
			  { "id": "46", "question": "para-", "answer": "Beside", "example": "Parathyroid glands" },
			  { "id": "47", "question": "per-", "answer": "Through", "example": "Percutaneous" },
			  { "id": "48", "question": "peri-", "answer": "Surrounding", "example": "Periosteum" },
			  { "id": "49", "question": "poly-", "answer": "Many, Much", "example": "Polymyositis" },
			  { "id": "50", "question": "post-", "answer": "After", "example": "Postpartum" },
			  { "id": "51", "question": "pre-", "answer": "Before", "example": "Prenatal" },
			  { "id": "52", "question": "pro-", "answer": "Before", "example": "Prognosis" },
			  { "id": "53", "question": "pseudo-", "answer": "False", "example": "Pseudocyesis" },
			  { "id": "54", "question": "quadric-", "answer": "Four", "example": "Quadriplegia" },
			  { "id": "55", "question": "re-", "answer": "Again", "example": "Reinfection" },
			  { "id": "56", "question": "retro-", "answer": "Behind", "example": "Retroperitoneal" },
			  { "id": "57", "question": "semi-", "answer": "Partial", "example": "Semicomatose" },
			  { "id": "58", "question": "sub-", "answer": "Below, under", "example": "Subcutaneous" },
			  { "id": "59", "question": "super-", "answer": "Above", "example": "Supercilia" },
			  { "id": "60", "question": "supra-", "answer": "Above", "example": "Suprascapular" },
			  { "id": "61", "question": "sym-", "answer": "Together", "example": "Symphysis" },
			  { "id": "62", "question": "tetra-", "answer": "Four", "example": "Tetraplegia" },
			  { "id": "63", "question": "trachy-", "answer": "Fast, Rapid", "example": "Tachycardia" },
			  { "id": "64", "question": "trans-", "answer": "Across", "example": "Transdermal" },
			  { "id": "65", "question": "tri-", "answer": "Three", "example": "Triceps" },
			  { "id": "66", "question": "un-", "answer": "Not", "example": "Unconscious" },
			  { "id": "67", "question": "uni-", "answer": "One", "example": "Unilateral" }
			]
        },
		{
          "id": "1-4",
          "name": "Terminology Suffixes",
          "flashCards": [
			{ "id": "1", "question": "-a", "answer": "Noun ending", "example": "Leukoderma" },
				{ "id": "2", "question": "-ac", "answer": "Pertaining to", "example": "Cardiac" },
				{ "id": "3", "question": "-ad", "answer": "Toward", "example": "Dorsad" },
				{ "id": "4", "question": "-algia", "answer": "Pain", "example": "Myalgia" },
				{ "id": "5", "question": "-amnios", "answer": "Amnion", "example": "Oligohydramnios" },
				{ "id": "6", "question": "-apheresis", "answer": "Removal", "example": "Plasmapheresis" },
				{ "id": "7", "question": "-ar", "answer": "Pertaining to", "example": "Appendicular" },
				{ "id": "8", "question": "-ary", "answer": "Pertaining to", "example": "Coronary" },
				{ "id": "9", "question": "-asthenia", "answer": "Weakness", "example": "Myasthenia gravis" },
				{ "id": "10", "question": "-carcinoma", "answer": "Tumor", "example": "Adenocarcinoma" },
				{ "id": "11", "question": "-cele", "answer": "Swelling", "example": "Hydrocele" },
				{ "id": "12", "question": "-centesis", "answer": "Surgical puncture", "example": "Amniocentesis" },
				{ "id": "13", "question": "-crine", "answer": "To secrete", "example": "Exocrine" },
				{ "id": "14", "question": "-cyesis", "answer": "Pregnancy", "example": "Pseudocyesis" },
				{ "id": "15", "question": "-cyte", "answer": "Cell", "example": "Leukocyte" },
				{ "id": "16", "question": "-desis", "answer": "Surgical fixation", "example": "Arthrodesis" },
				{ "id": "17", "question": "-drome", "answer": "Run, running", "example": "Syndrome" },
				{ "id": "18", "question": "-e", "answer": "Noun ending", "example": "Neonate" },
				{ "id": "19", "question": "-eal", "answer": "Pertaining to", "example": "Esophageal" },
				{ "id": "20", "question": "-ectasis", "answer": "Stretching out", "example": "Bronchiectasis" },
				{ "id": "21", "question": "-ectomy", "answer": "Surgical removal", "example": "Gastrectomy" },
				{ "id": "22", "question": "-emesis", "answer": "Vomiting", "example": "Hematemesis" },
				{ "id": "23", "question": "-emia", "answer": "In the blood", "example": "Anemia" },
				{ "id": "24", "question": "-esis", "answer": "Condition", "example": "Diuresis" },
				{ "id": "25", "question": "-gen", "answer": "Coming to be", "example": "Teratogen" },
				{ "id": "26", "question": "-genic", "answer": "Producing", "example": "Carcinogenic" },
				{ "id": "27", "question": "-gram", "answer": "The record", "example": "Electrocardiogram" },
				{ "id": "28", "question": "-graph", "answer": "Device for recording", "example": "Electrocardiograph" },
				{ "id": "29", "question": "-graphy", "answer": "Process of recording", "example": "Electrocardiography" },
				{ "id": "30", "question": "-ia", "answer": "Diseased state", "example": "Tachycardia" },
				{ "id": "31", "question": "-iasis", "answer": "Condition", "example": "Choledocholithiasis" },
				{ "id": "32", "question": "-iatrist", "answer": "Specialist", "example": "Psychiatrist" },
				{ "id": "33", "question": "-iatry", "answer": "Specialty, treatment", "example": "Psychiatry" },
				{ "id": "34", "question": "-ic", "answer": "Pertaining to", "example": "Cardiac" },
				{ "id": "35", "question": "-ictal", "answer": "Seizure, attack", "example": "Postictal" },
				{ "id": "36", "question": "-ior", "answer": "Pertaining to", "example": "Anterior" },
				{ "id": "37", "question": "-ism", "answer": "State of", "example": "Hyperthyroidism" },
				{ "id": "38", "question": "-itis", "answer": "Inflammation", "example": "Colitis" },
				{ "id": "39", "question": "-oma", "answer": "Tumor", "example": "Glioma" },
				{ "id": "40", "question": "-osis", "answer": "Condition", "example": "Fibrosis" },
				{ "id": "41", "question": "-logist", "answer": "One who studies and treats", "example": "Oncologist" },
				{ "id": "42", "question": "-logy", "answer": "Study of", "example": "Cardiology" },
				{ "id": "43", "question": "-lysis", "answer": "Separating", "example": "Thrombolysis" },
				{ "id": "44", "question": "-malacia", "answer": "Softening", "example": "Chondromalacia" },
				{ "id": "45", "question": "-megaly", "answer": "Enlarged", "example": "Gastromegaly" },
				{ "id": "46", "question": "-meter", "answer": "Device for measuring", "example": "Thermometer" },
				{ "id": "47", "question": "-metry", "answer": "Measuring", "example": "Spirometry" },
				{ "id": "48", "question": "-oid", "answer": "Resembling", "example": "Lipoid" },
				{ "id": "49", "question": "-oma", "answer": "Tumor, swelling", "example": "Melanoma" },
				{ "id": "50", "question": "-opia", "answer": "Vision", "example": "Diplopia" },
				{ "id": "51", "question": "-opsy", "answer": "Viewing", "example": "Biopsy" },
				{ "id": "52", "question": "-ous", "answer": "Pertaining to", "example": "Intravenous" },
				{ "id": "53", "question": "-paresis", "answer": "Slight paralysis", "example": "Hemiparesis" },
				{ "id": "54", "question": "-pathy", "answer": "Disease", "example": "Polyneuropathy" },
				{ "id": "55", "question": "-penia", "answer": "Abnormal reduction in number", "example": "Erythrocytopenia" },
				{ "id": "56", "question": "-pepsia", "answer": "Digestion", "example": "Dyspepsia" },
				{ "id": "57", "question": "-pexy", "answer": "Surgical fixation", "example": "Colpopexy" },
				{ "id": "58", "question": "-phagia", "answer": "Swallowing", "example": "Dysphagia" },
				{ "id": "59", "question": "-phobia", "answer": "Aversion", "example": "Photophobia" },
				{ "id": "60", "question": "-physis", "answer": "Growth", "example": "Symphysis" },
				{ "id": "61", "question": "-plasia", "answer": "Development, growth", "example": "Hyperplasia" },
				{ "id": "62", "question": "-plasm", "answer": "Growth", "example": "Cytoplasm" },
				{ "id": "63", "question": "-plasty", "answer": "Surgical repair", "example": "Rhinoplasty" },
				{ "id": "64", "question": "-plegia", "answer": "Paralysis", "example": "Ophthalmoplegia" },
				{ "id": "65", "question": "-pnea", "answer": "Breathing", "example": "Dyspnea" },
				{ "id": "66", "question": "-poiesis", "answer": "Formation", "example": "Leukopoiesis" },
				{ "id": "67", "question": "-ptosis", "answer": "Prolapsed, drooping", "example": "Nephroptosis" },
				{ "id": "68", "question": "-rrhage", "answer": "Excessive bleeding", "example": "Hemorrhage" },
				{ "id": "69", "question": "-rrhagia", "answer": "Excessive bleeding", "example": "Menorrhagia" },
				{ "id": "70", "question": "-rrhaphy", "answer": "Surgical suturing", "example": "Herniorrhaphy" },
				{ "id": "71", "question": "-rrhea", "answer": "Discharge, flow", "example": "Diarrhea" },
				{ "id": "72", "question": "-rrhexis", "answer": "Rupture", "example": "Hysterorrhexis" },
				{ "id": "73", "question": "-sclerosis", "answer": "Hardening", "example": "Arteriosclerosis" },
				{ "id": "74", "question": "-scope", "answer": "Instrument for viewing", "example": "Microscope" },
				{ "id": "75", "question": "-scopy", "answer": "Visual examination", "example": "Colonoscopy" },
				{ "id": "76", "question": "-spasm", "answer": "Involuntary contraction", "example": "Bronchospasm" },
				{ "id": "77", "question": "-stasis", "answer": "Stopping, controlling", "example": "Hemostasis" },
				{ "id": "78", "question": "-stenosis", "answer": "Narrowing", "example": "Aortic stenosis" },
				{ "id": "79", "question": "-tome", "answer": "Instrument to cut", "example": "Osteotome" },
				{ "id": "80", "question": "-tomy", "answer": "Cutting, incision", "example": "Tracheotomy" },
				{ "id": "81", "question": "-tripsy", "answer": "Surgical crushing", "example": "Lithotripsy" },
				{ "id": "82", "question": "-trophy", "answer": "Nourishment, development", "example": "Hypertrophy" },
				{ "id": "83", "question": "-ule", "answer": "Small", "example": "Venule" },
				{ "id": "84", "question": "-um", "answer": "Structure, thing", "example": "Pericardium" },
				{ "id": "85", "question": "-uria", "answer": "Urine condition", "example": "Hematuria" },
				{ "id": "86", "question": "-us", "answer": "Structure, substance", "example": "Thrombus" },
				{ "id": "87", "question": "-y", "answer": "Condition, process", "example": "Autopsy" },
				{ "id": "88", "question": "-zygous", "answer": "Pertaining to a zygote", "example": "Homozygous" },
				{ "id": "89", "question": "-clast", "answer": "Break", "example": "Osteoclast" },
				{ "id": "90", "question": "-genesis", "answer": "Formation", "example": "Angiogenesis" },
				{ "id": "91", "question": "-kinesis", "answer": "Movement", "example": "Hyperkinesis" },
				{ "id": "92", "question": "-lepsy", "answer": "Seizure", "example": "Epilepsy" },
				{ "id": "93", "question": "-mania", "answer": "Obsessive preoccupation", "example": "Pyromania" }
			]
        },
		{
		  "id": "1-5",
          "name": "Word Terminals",
		  "flashcards": [
			  {"id": "1", "question": "-ic, -tic", "type": "adjective", "answer": "pertaining to; having to with", "example": "hepatic, genetic, hypnotic"},
			  {"id": "2", "question": "-al", "type": "adjective", "answer": "pertaining to; having to with", "example": "dermal, bilateral"},
			  {"id": "3", "question": "-ac", "type": "adjective", "answer": "pertaining to; having to with", "example": "cardiac, celiac"},
			  {"id": "4", "question": "-ar", "type": "adjective", "answer": "pertaining to; having to with", "example": "ulnar, scapular, patellar"},
			  {"id": "5", "question": "-ular", "type": "adjective", "answer": "pertaining to; having to with", "example": "valvular, radicular"},
			  {"id": "6", "question": "-ary", "type": "adjective", "answer": "pertaining to; having to with", "example": "coronary, biliary"},
			  {"id": "7", "question": "-ical", "type": "adjective", "answer": "pertaining to; having to with", "example": "surgical, pharmaceutical"},
			  {"id": "8", "question": "-um", "type": "noun", "answer": "the thing being described by word element", "example": "endothelium, labium, cerebrum"},
			  {"id": "9", "question": "-is", "type": "noun", "answer": "the thing being described by word element", "example": "dermis, pelvis"},
			  {"id": "10", "question": "-us", "type": "noun", "answer": "the thing being described by word element", "example": "umbilicus, thrombus"},
			  {"id": "11", "question": "-a (singular)", "type": "noun", "answer": "the thing being described by word element", "example": "bursa, gingiva, conjunctiva"},
			  {"id": "12", "question": "-a (plural of -um or -on)", "type": "noun", "answer": "the thing being described by word element", "example": "labia, endothelia"},
			  {"id": "13", "question": "-ae (plural of -a or -um)", "type": "noun", "answer": "the thing being described by word element", "example": "bursa, gingivae"},
			  {"id": "14", "question": "-y", "type": "noun", "answer": "act of; result of; procedure", "example": "endoscopy, microscopy"},
			  {"id": "15", "question": "-ia", "type": "noun", "answer": "disease; condition", "example": "amnesia, anosia, dysphagia"},
			  {"id": "16", "question": "-ism", "type": "noun", "answer": "disease; condition", "example": "alcoholism, autism, albinism"},
			  {"id": "17", "question": "-ac", "type": "noun", "answer": "person affected by", "example": "maniac, hemophiliac"},
			  {"id": "18", "question": "-ate", "type": "verb", "answer": "to perform, bring about; put into action", "example": "terminate, exfoliate, fixate"},
			  {"id": "19", "question": "-tion", "type": "noun", "answer": "process, action, condition", "example": "ablation, ligation, retraction"},
			  {"id": "20", "question": "-esis", "type": "noun", "answer": "condition or process", "example": "amniocentesis, uresis, electrophoresis"},
			  {"id": "21", "question": "-id", "type": "adjective", "answer": "to be; being", "example": "rigid, flaccid, fluid, parotid, putrid"}
			]
		}
      ]
    }
  ]
}
